Nicholas Roussos: There you are.
Kostadis Roussos: Hello, Nicholas.
Nicholas Roussos: Whoa.
Kostadis Roussos: What did you think of the… I mean, I know they're AI slop, and I know you don't like AI slop, but I felt those…
Kostadis Roussos: Quest logs were useful.
Nicholas Roussos: Yeah, it is.
Dimos: Blue.
Kostadis Roussos: Hello? Give me a second.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Nicholas Roussos: If you're looking for something.
Nicholas Roussos: How you doing, Themo?
Nicholas Roussos: There you go. But if you're not here yet.
Dimos: I'm sorry.
Nicholas Roussos: Oh, no, you are here.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, can you guys hear me? Yeah, you can hear me.
Nicholas Roussos: Hello, can you hear me?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, we can.
Dimos: It's done.
Nicholas Roussos: You weren't responding to me.
Kostadis Roussos: he was feeling, you know, Dimos… Alright.
Nicholas Roussos: How are you guys doing?
Kostadis Roussos: Alive and kicking? I mean, I'm doing well, but, like, I don't think that was directed to me, I think it was a direct.
Nicholas Roussos: Yeah, no doubt.
Kostadis Roussos: Why don't I give you guys a few moments, I'm gonna pour myself some extra coffee.
Nicholas Roussos: How you doing, Theo?
Dimos: I believe your father… Answer correctly, alive and kicking.
Dimos: I'm doing better now.
Nicholas Roussos: gang, it ain't always about that, I'm just, like, trying to start a conversation, dude.
Dimos: Yeah, I just didn't hear you because your father started talking at the same time.
Dimos: Lee, thank you what you said.
Nicholas Roussos: I was trying to… I'm just trying to start a conversation, man.
Dimos: Yeah, I know.
Nicholas Roussos: I have…
Dimos: try to play a bit of survival Minecraft, but… I'm so booked.
Nicholas Roussos: How bad are you at Minecraft, dude?
Dimos: No, I'm not bad, I'm just bored to play.
Nicholas Roussos: That's why you gotta do the drinking.
Dimos: I mean, I could be…
Nicholas Roussos: Or I just think it's a Long Island.
Nicholas Roussos: Govid, you really would get…
Kostadis Roussos: Hello?
Dimos: Hello?
Nicholas Roussos: Whoa.
Kostadis Roussos: hour, folks.
Kostadis Roussos: Good. Did you guys resolve all the important things that I can review later in the recording and the transcript?
Nicholas Roussos: Oh, shit, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Beautiful.
Nicholas Roussos: Yeah, you're cooking.
Nicholas Roussos: That's gonna be a very funny recording, then.
Nicholas Roussos: I didn't refine nothing that happened.
Kostadis Roussos: I will… I will not…
Nicholas Roussos: No, no.
Dimos: We're just talking about, Felker shenanigans.
Kostadis Roussos: No.
Dimos: Felcro and his new favorite game.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Nicholas Roussos: If you know, you know.
Dimos: It's…
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: And if…
Nicholas Roussos: We're looking for something.
Kostadis Roussos: I hate these people.
Kostadis Roussos: They could have done the work. They didn't do the work. Why didn't they do the work? Can you tell me why they didn't do the work?
Dimos: Because they used AI?
Kostadis Roussos: Hey.
Kostadis Roussos: You know what AI is really good at?
Dimos: Doing the work.
Kostadis Roussos: No. Generating hallucinated settings that allow me to come up with all sorts of things. Okay, I need to tell you guys something that I discovered that only 3 people with dyslexia, like the three of us, could not have noticed through a year of plague.
Dimos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: The actual spelling of Farrell Kerr's last name is not the one I've been using throughout the entire campaign.
Nicholas Roussos: All and done.
Kostadis Roussos: I have it written as a different name, right?
Kostadis Roussos: So, I have now have a canonical reason why, what's-His-Name did not know that it was spelled… the registry actually has the wrong spelling.
Kostadis Roussos: The ledger has the wrong spelling.
Kostadis Roussos: Right. So now, part of the problem with everybody is that nobody knew what a spelling was. Now, Felcor… is Felcor dyslexic in the game or not?
Kostadis Roussos: The funny part would be Felcor didn't notice either.
Kostadis Roussos: That's a… that's a Nicholas call. Nick.
Nicholas Roussos: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: He didn't notice either. All right. So, a gag, so at this point in time, yeah, so Felcor's last name in the ledger was misspelled. Felcor didn't notice.
Dimos: How badly misspelled are we talking about?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, just a little bit.
Kostadis Roussos: I discovered this because I started… I started fixing my tooling to be a lot more strict on naming, and I discovered that you are not the only campaign in which I've completely mangled the name of a player through hundreds of summaries.
Kostadis Roussos: In a different campaign we've been playing for a year and some time, and I've been spelling the character Grygum instead of Gurgum.
Dimos: K.
Kostadis Roussos: Now, in my defense, the other three dyslexics who play the game with me didn't notice that either.
Nicholas Roussos: How would that unfold?
Kostadis Roussos: No, it's not. I just thought it was funny. Like, now we have an in-game real reason why nobody's been able to find Felcor, because Felker himself can't even remember how to spell his name.
Kostadis Roussos: And we're gonna go with the theory that Felcor has signed his name in a variety of different ways, all thinking they're correct. Why? Because he's dyslexic, and quite frankly, he never really cared very much.
Kostadis Roussos: Is that fair, Nick? He's your character, so…
Nicholas Roussos: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: I don't want to put words in his mouth.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So, couple things.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: The party has made it back to Sportum.
Kostadis Roussos: -
Kostadis Roussos: Why have they gone back to Sportum? Because that's where…
Kostadis Roussos: the various factions, that's where the staging to Mary Midra will occur.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: So, after the slow clap, Right?
Kostadis Roussos: the assassinate… the disintegration of Alasta?
Kostadis Roussos: Right?
Kostadis Roussos: Everybody kind of got the point that who rules… who rules Sith Morkane is the second problem. The first problem is defeating, is defeating the fire giants in Mare Midra.
Dimos: Great.
Dimos: Right. Thank God that we agree.
Kostadis Roussos: There was, you know, there was… The, the stone job…
Dimos: Did they?
Kostadis Roussos: a slow cloud.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, let me just say… show you something. So, to make my life… to help you guys a little bit, I came up with a scheme
Kostadis Roussos: Recently… Let me just show this.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, I have it over here.
Kostadis Roussos: But… I have created a quest log.
Kostadis Roussos: Which I will put in the general… this is a document that is written in Braumgreen's voice.
Kostadis Roussos: That describes all the open quests you currently have, and kind of situates you in the context of the adventure.
Dimos: Have you made it public or not?
Kostadis Roussos: I put it in the Discord… I put it in the Discord chat, it should be accessible.
Dimos: Yes, but… Because it asked me if I want to be editor, viewer, commenter.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, sorry. Anyone with a…
Dimos: I mean, with public?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, I just did that, sorry.
Dimos: That's fine.
Kostadis Roussos: Beyond our rules.
Dimos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: And I have put it in the,
Kostadis Roussos: And I just shared with you a link to the document, so that if you're ever trying to find it, you can find it right away. Cindy, it should be in your…
Kostadis Roussos: And, the first… and there's a link, if you click on the Quest log, it'll take you to the Google Drive document.
Dimos: I mean, I'm just… I want to disagree, at least as far as I'm remembering, with only one thing.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes?
Kostadis Roussos: Now, as I said, as I said, these are Bromgren's notes.
Kostadis Roussos: So, there's po- it's entirely possible that he got something wrong.
Kostadis Roussos: That's why…
Dimos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: That's my in-canon explanation for AI hallucinations. What did we get wrong?
Nicholas Roussos: Oh, come on!
Dimos: I'm just saying, we don't owe anything to PPU.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Dimos: We don't owe anything to Pipyap.
Dimos: Oh, I don't know how to… no.
Kostadis Roussos: Yep, yep.
Dimos: team.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: I love this. He wants what he calls FU money.
Nicholas Roussos: Yeah.
Dimos: Oh, where?
Nicholas Roussos: that term?
Kostadis Roussos: our own business.
Kostadis Roussos: Like I said, in our own business, I'd forgotten that you had said this.
Dimos: Yes.
Dimos: I can agree. I don't see the problem.
Dimos: Who is Quilbrin?
Kostadis Roussos: Quilbrin is the drow who killed… thought he killed Solomon Nedrazak.
Kostadis Roussos: Dope, do you find this useful?
Dimos: Yes, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so of all the things I've created with AI, this turns out to be the most useful.
Kostadis Roussos: I will just quickly read you the summary of last week's events.
Kostadis Roussos: Or are we with Ireland?
Kostadis Roussos: And…
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: I hate when this guy ships new code, because I basically have to re-click, and I hate re-clicking, right, under dark, Hillsfari.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, some assembly required. I will read you the short version so we can start playing. After killing… after slaying King Dengor, the party faced the terrifying undead revenant Princess Belasta, who demanded to know who had killed the fire giant.
Kostadis Roussos: Bromgrim cleveily persuaded her that her true quarry still lived elsewhere in Mermindra, and Felcor quietly realized that Velostad actually wanted to be convinced. As a revenant, completing a revenge would cause her to cease to exist, so she was secretly relieved.
Kostadis Roussos: Before vanishing, she released a previously banished fire giant, who upon finding his king dead, refused to stand down.
Kostadis Roussos: Despite his defiance and a punishing blow that shattered Brown Grimm's concentration.
Kostadis Roussos: The party and their stone-giant allies overwhelmed and defeated him. The victory was short-lived, however, as the death of King Dengor simultaneously collapsed the magical binding, sustaining all the zealot Azors, wiping them out of the existence instant, and sending the forge into chaos, with fire salamanders rampaging through the crumbling chamber, Alesta, sorry.
Kostadis Roussos: Akratus and Bayan used magic to cloak and conceal the group, while they swiftly extracted three finished Hellfire projectors and components for four moors, and roughly a thousand gold pieces worth of rare metals, narrowly escaping as the salamanders finally gave chase.
Kostadis Roussos: Back in Sithmor Kane, the party returned to every faction they had made a promise to, gathered in the same room, all expecting to collect. Political tensions erupted immediately between Railera, Asala, and the cult of Varun's representative, Hamad, while Theokur…
Kostadis Roussos: Serenely ignored the standoff and tinkered with ballistic components. The situation turned catastrophic when a magical drow clone of drow Archmage Solomon Nedrazak appeared and annihilated Alasta on the spot, reducing them to dust and silencing the room in horror. The clone attempted to seize control of the moment.
Kostadis Roussos: But Felcourt, bolstered by Dan's inspiration, fired a ballista into the air and delivered a blunt, commanding speech, cutting through the chaos and reminding everyone that a city and army still needed to be taken back. His iron resolve broke through even Solomon
Kostadis Roussos: It's clone's composure. And when a stone giant slowly began to clap, others joined in, one by one, until the entire fractious coalition, drow, cultists, giants, and…
Kostadis Roussos: Undead worshippers alike stood united behind the march on Mayor Midra.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Dimos: Okay.
Dimos: So, we are ready to fight.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, you're ready to plan.
Kostadis Roussos: You don't go to war in a… war is not a simple thing, my friends.
Dimos: I mean, so many people have done it, how hard could it be?
Kostadis Roussos: You know, ask the Donald.
Dimos: I mean, even Donald was able to do it.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, you're just comprised.
Dimos: Maybe.
Dimos: Am I wrong?
Kostadis Roussos: No.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Great.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so… You arrive at, so, as you…
Kostadis Roussos: So, you arrive there, and you see a variety of folks in the, sitting around in the Spore Dome.
Kostadis Roussos: So, and you see some of them you've seen before. You see Ella Neale, double E is there.
Dimos: Great.
Kostadis Roussos: Solomon Nedrazak, of course, is there.
Dimos: Peace.
Kostadis Roussos: sovereign Agaricos of the Myconids is there.
Kostadis Roussos: A mind flayer is present.
Kostadis Roussos: And then someone you haven't seen in a very long time.
Kostadis Roussos: Elisande and Her Blind Goat.
Kostadis Roussos: She was… she was somebody cryptic you met very early on. She keeps reappearing at critical junctures.
Kostadis Roussos: very mysterious individual. If you give me a second, I will tell you when you.
Dimos: I remember the GOAT, I don't remember here.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, I know. Yeah, so she was… she was in the early part of the adventure.
Kostadis Roussos: And I even have a picture of her, so… so that you could… so you can see what she looks like.
Kostadis Roussos: I don't have a picture. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so, alright.
Kostadis Roussos: So, let me just put some icons here so we have the, the… the… let's see…
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so this is…
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on.
Kostadis Roussos: This is First Lord Byum Bum.
Kostadis Roussos: introduce themselves as the first lord of Hillsfar.
Kostadis Roussos: He's the new guy in charge.
Kostadis Roussos: Roll an insight check, or perception, or investigation.
Dimos: Should we see anything on the map or not?
Kostadis Roussos: You should, but you're… if you were on the right map.
Dimos: That's why I'm asking.
Kostadis Roussos: There we go.
Kostadis Roussos: You're on the Sport W.
Dimos: Okay.
Dimos: So, you said what inside or the investigation?
Kostadis Roussos: Whichever one you want.
Dimos: Investigation Felker.
Nicholas Roussos: Yep, that's meet Mr. Investigate.
Nicholas Roussos: Yeah, investigation plus 10.
Nicholas Roussos: 17?
Kostadis Roussos: 17, right?
Nicholas Roussos: So that's just said…
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, you recognize this guy as a,
Kostadis Roussos: What's the word I'm looking for?
Kostadis Roussos: He's the guard… he's the first guard you guys met when you went into Hillsfar.
Dimos: Yep.
Kostadis Roussos: Somehow, somehow, with all of the chaos and mayhem of Hillsfar, he has now become the first lord of Hillsfar.
Dimos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, so he's like, you know, he's very… he's very happy to see you, he says, you know, he's like, I know, he knows Zestana Rao has said nothing but glorious words.
Kostadis Roussos: You immediately realize he's sucking up at you.
Nicholas Roussos: Really?
Dimos: She would never!
Kostadis Roussos: Right,
Kostadis Roussos: And is very happy that you guys have taken on the hard task of, trying to save
Kostadis Roussos: Never winter. Hills Farm.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Then you have double E.
Kostadis Roussos: She's also present.
Kostadis Roussos: What else is here?
Kostadis Roussos: Solomon, we have her… So, we need a micronid.
Kostadis Roussos: Who, remember, you guys helped a while ago?
Nicholas Roussos: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Sovereign Agricos, says, Much has changed since you last came.
Dimos: Okay…
Kostadis Roussos: You recall that Saverin Agrakos is the kind of person that he says something. If you're not interested in further follow-ups, he says nothing more, so he just sort of sits there.
Kostadis Roussos: You also know that change for Myconids is very disturbing. They don't deal well with change, so the fact that he saw something change is possibly significant.
Dimos: And we ask what…
Kostadis Roussos: Like, you're like, can you tell us what… can you tell us what changed?
Kostadis Roussos: Hmm, he pauses, and he kind of moves his hands, and he sways, and he lets out the connecting spores.
Kostadis Roussos: And what you realize is that there was a battle between the Zuktomi, the demon queen of the fungi.
Dimos: K…
Kostadis Roussos: had tried to take control of a Gory… I agree.
Kostadis Roussos: Fuck, I can't pronounce his name.
Kostadis Roussos: The, the, the creature… that, Agari Kumos, who is essentially a sentient massively sentient, mushroom.
Kostadis Roussos: But was defeated by 5 adventurers.
Kostadis Roussos: Along with another… along with another demon, Jubilex.
Kostadis Roussos: And so now the myconoids are very… and so you immediately remember that Alder told you that there was a Plan A, and you were her Plan B.
Dimos: Okay… So, they were… Plan A, they were those guys.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, the, the, the, the more core…
Kostadis Roussos: That apparently they're succeeding in whatever her plan A was.
Kostadis Roussos: And just to remind you what her… well, just to remind you what her.
Dimos: Put it in.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, just to remind you what her plan A was, because you… Alder… Alder, in her adventuring party, had went and trapped Lolth in a prison.
Kostadis Roussos: Right?
Kostadis Roussos: That… where she had gotten an arrangement working with Varun, the other god of the other elfish, the drow god, alright?
Dimos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: And what she told you is that all of the madness in the Underdark was triggered by Lolf.
Kostadis Roussos: To escape from the… from her prison.
Nicholas Roussos: That's lovely.
Kostadis Roussos: And that her plan A was… and that, you know, now there was a disaster, and she's, you know, got a lot of things on her plate, and so she's been trying to manage the disaster, and so she sent a group of adventurers
Kostadis Roussos: down into the Underdark to go deal with, on a crazy plan, to go stop the entire destruction of the Underdark by the demons.
Kostadis Roussos: And from what she heard, just to remind you, is that they had this plan to essentially launch… use a magical device that would cause all of the demons to show up in a location, and demons being demons would end up killing each other, and as long as the party killed whoever was left over, you know, the problem with the Underdark would be solved.
Nicholas Roussos: What, so that's our job now?
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, that, that was, that was your other adventuring party, Nicholas. That was, you know, that's your, what your characters with, Sylvia, and what's his.
Nicholas Roussos: Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? Right. But, she said that there was a… there was a… but in her… in her master plan, she uncovered a small flaw, which she wants to thank you guys for.
Kostadis Roussos: Which she thanked you guys for, saying that it turns out that Grast had figured out that that was the plan, and so he had come up with the plan B, and so if the party figured out how to launch… solve the question of the crystal, Grast's plan was to show up in Miramidjo.
Kostadis Roussos: And so, you were her plan B to go deal… to show up in Miramidra and defeat Grest.
Kostadis Roussos: This is a reminder.
Dimos: Okay…
Kostadis Roussos: Right? So that's her… that's what she said is your… that… so she asked you to do that mission. Bromgren was so excited about meeting Alder, because she's sort of a legendary figure, that he had her sign his sword.
Kostadis Roussos: you look confused.
Dimos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Go for it.
Dimos: You mean he had to assign his…
Kostadis Roussos: So he a… no, no, he, he asked, she was so… he asked her for an autograph.
Dimos: Oh, to sign, okay. Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: He was very excited.
Kostadis Roussos: He was very excited to have, you know, Alder. Alder is a legendary figure among the Harpers.
Dimos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: She was involved in the defeat of… she was involved in the defeat of the Drow Empire's incursion in the north. Her son saved the world from the dragons.
Dimos: She's a… Okay, this is a famous lenses already.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, she, she was involved in the events of the storm… of the storm… the… the giant war…
Kostadis Roussos: well, that happens after work… after this. But anyway, she's a legendary figure, and so you… you… and she's famous throughout the North, and you know, her show… and she, of course, has this annoying habit as a 21st level…
Kostadis Roussos: A rogue of showing up wherever she wants, making an announcement, and then leaving.
Dimos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: And her personality is modeled after Natasha's, because that was her player. So if you feel that it's kind of like a middle-aged mom being really irritated, you… I have correctly nailed the character.
Dimos: K…
Kostadis Roussos: Does that make sense?
Dimos: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so,
Kostadis Roussos: So, so yeah, Braumgrim Grimm is… and that's why Braum Grimm is kind of thinking to himself that maybe having the signature of the legendary hero of the Harpers who banished Lolf into a dimensional prison while talking to followers of Arrow is not a really good plan.
Kostadis Roussos: But then again, this is not a commonly known piece of information, so, you know, there's plausible deniability.
Dimos: Okay, good to know.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, okay, so,
Kostadis Roussos: Then the next person in this, menagerie is whom? So remember you guys met, worked with some Mind Flayers?
Dimos: Work with… work for.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, the Mind Flayers made you an offer, and you decided that that offer
Kostadis Roussos: Was an offer you wanted to, pursue?
Dimos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: I mean… One person's offer, another person's, you know.
Dimos: We didn't have a lot of choices because, the Emerald Enclave.
Dimos: Everyone just was saying, get the information.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, yes. I mean, you did have the information. You could have let the North burn to the ground.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so, as you… okay, so, okay, so, alright, so…
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so as you… one… okay, so… so these are the people who've shown up.
Kostadis Roussos: There are… there are also, you notice, a…
Kostadis Roussos: These are some of the leaders. There's also the faction leaders, from the various, groups you guys brought with you, so there's, we should probably bring up,
Kostadis Roussos: Right, Lyra?
Kostadis Roussos: She's the,
Kostadis Roussos: She's the drow… the leader of the, drows… the former drow slaves, the mob you guys… you guys hired.
Kostadis Roussos: Right?
Kostadis Roussos: There's the drow… Elite. There's, there's Quilbrin.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, let's put him here.
Kostadis Roussos: There it is.
Kostadis Roussos: So… Line… I killed… so I'm just gonna put killed Solomon, so you guys, you can remember.
Kostadis Roussos: It's called Solem, and this over here is Hamad.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so this is, Ahmad. Here's the other drow, allies that you managed to acquire, and you also promised
Kostadis Roussos: Sithmore came to?
Dimos: We never promised that.
Kostadis Roussos: Who…
Dimos: Allegedly.
Kostadis Roussos: Allegedly, allegedly.
Kostadis Roussos: And agency,
Kostadis Roussos: I'm just gonna put… these are… I just need to have different icons for the… the drow.
Kostadis Roussos: Much to your irritation, the, the Never Answers also showed up with the Never Answers. The faction that was allied to Velosta shows up. But, of course, Velostis kind of abandoned them on a mad crusade to kill every fire giant possible.
Dimos: Oh, great, so we can go to Merrida and everyone will be dead.
Kostadis Roussos: well, I mean, she's powerful, but not THAT powerful.
Kostadis Roussos: More to the point, everybody's waiting for her, not for you.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me just make the… What?
Dimos: Yeah, I was just thinking we're probably gonna do illusion and persuasion, performance again.
Dimos: Make them believe that she's here, and she told them to go.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so this is, Depressor… Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so on your way, as you arrive, everybody seems to be in conversation about one topic.
Dimos: the war?
Kostadis Roussos: No, apparently something far more important.
Kostadis Roussos: you're like, what could be more important? Apparently, there is… the Council is debate… is discussing the fact that Solomon Nedrazak's experiment to remove the fiendish taint from the fire giant actually worked.
Dimos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: And that, and so there's… so everybody's now debating, well, then why do we have to fight? Why don't we just, you know, use the same technique on all the fire giants?
Dimos: What's the limitation?
Kostadis Roussos: Solomon explains the limitation, as he says, Is that…
Kostadis Roussos: He goes… he goes, well, the limitation is that, one, it requires the fire giant to be subdued.
Dimos: K…
Kostadis Roussos: And two, it requires the fire giant to be under, and it requires 10 days.
Dimos: There's subdued meanings.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, you captured the fire giant, you put him in a little box.
Kostadis Roussos: We were able to, experiment on him.
Kostadis Roussos: It's unfortunately not a mass solution, but what it does mean…
Kostadis Roussos: Is that it offers us a path.
Dimos: Okay…
Kostadis Roussos: If we find any more of these fire giants, he pauses and says, the good news is that this fire giant taint is a… is… so he says, like, yes, it works, but it is not a military solution.
Dimos: Because it takes 10 days to happen.
Kostadis Roussos: Because it's… you can't just, it's not like something you can sprinkle in the air and somebody's affected by it.
Dimos: Okay, so… what… how can we spread it? How… how… what…
Dimos: What… how can we use it?
Dimos: If we cannot spread it.
Kostadis Roussos: So… so now, now we get to the adventure.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so…
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so around the fungals Amphitheater of Spore Dugdom, a myriad of faces are engaged in a dozen of furious conversations.
Kostadis Roussos: Excitement wars with panic, and those not seated in pace back and forth. Secretive drow mixed with tall mushroom men, while stout dwarves talk with humans wearing helmets capped with red feathers. A little girl in a dirty dress sits alone atop a tall mushroom, her arm around a black goat with milky white eyes.
Kostadis Roussos: An elven woman approaches the center of the gathering and raises her arms toward the cavern above. A silence magically descends, and the assemblage looks toward the woman on the floor. Eleanil Ellacondale, called the moonsilver herald by some, lowers her arms and addresses the crowd.
Kostadis Roussos: A critas, you know, silently cheers.
Dimos: in.
Kostadis Roussos: We are about to undertake the largest military operation in recent memory.
Kostadis Roussos: The danger posed by the Dark Prince and his followers in Miramindra has reached a critical stage.
Kostadis Roussos: Our allies force from Sithmor Kane.
Kostadis Roussos: She nods her head to Solomon, and Rayleira, and to Hamad, and to the new lead, and to Quilbrin.
Kostadis Roussos: have provided us with the location and avenues of approach to the city deep in the Underdark, and we have recently learned that Red Hillspawn, the leader of the Fire Giant, and demonic forces, is present in the city, preparing for their invasion of the Sunlight Realms.
Kostadis Roussos: No, I did not pull this off from The Return of the Jedi.
Nicholas Roussos: Yeah, but the AI did.
Kostadis Roussos: No, dude, this was handwritten. This was lovingly handwritten by a… by a human being.
Kostadis Roussos: The AI would have written it slightly differently. This leaves their commands tracture vulnerable to attack, and gives us the possibility to end the threat once and for all.
Kostadis Roussos: Teams will deploy from Spordome to three advanced positions, where we will set up three bases for attacks into the city. At the said time, we will require two other small teams to scout alternate approaches to the enemy forces, and gather local allies. Using any gathered intelligence, we will land share attack and drive our forces into the city until the threat has ended.
Kostadis Roussos: To this we are committed. There is no going back now. We mobilize in an hour. Find your teams and make your preparations.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so I have to give you a handout.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, so, alright, so now let me do this, okay. So, yes, you can ask any questions if you want.
Dimos: I don't think I have a question so far.
Kostadis Roussos: Kritas asks, Can we actually take the city?
Dimos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Millennial, no.
Kostadis Roussos: No, not with this. We have 7 contingents, three which have never held a line, and Mayor Mindra has a demon lord in the courtyard.
Kostadis Roussos: We have enough to make them look the wrong way for a while. That has been enough before. Ask me about Flan sometime.
Kostadis Roussos: He caught them.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so, so she's like… everybody sort of pauses.
Kostadis Roussos: She goes, we all know the plan. If we defeat Hamday, we will have defeated their leaders, and they will start squabbling amongst themselves.
Kostadis Roussos: Our goal is not to seize Mayor Mindra, our goal is to defeat Hamad.
Dimos: Boom.
Kostadis Roussos: Our objective is to defeat the leadership of… to defeat their leadership, and to provoke chaos.
Kostadis Roussos: You're a little confused.
Dimos: Okay, so… What do you mean, provoke chaos?
Kostadis Roussos: Voom, the First Lord, stands up. Yes, my friend Diane, protector of Hillsfar.
Dimos: New title, I didn't know that.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, I mean, I just wish to say a few words about my good friend, Diane.
Kostadis Roussos: Diane is, of course, an important part of our adventuring group.
Kostadis Roussos: Whom we… who has… who has done many great things for the city of Hillsfar.
Dimos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: And I know.
Dimos: We have 3 caves.
Kostadis Roussos: He's, like, he's, like, making a pitch that, you know, you're heroes of Hillsfar, and, like, defenders of Hillsfar.
Dimos: But I'm trying to understand the plan here.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: She goes, the plan is… The plan is that hill giants, right, fire giants.
Dimos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: are chaotic creatures.
Kostadis Roussos: Currently infused with demonic power.
Kostadis Roussos: The plan is.
Dimos: altogether.
Dimos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: The plan is held together by Hamad. The goal is to get into the city and somehow get to Hamad and kill him.
Dimos: So by killing Hamad, we… Destroy all the fat giants?
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, we don't destroy all the fire giants, but they become disorganized.
Kostadis Roussos: If they become disorganized.
Dimos: They're gonna bring chaos, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, they're gonna start fighting amongst themselves.
Dimos: Okay.
Dimos: what, what is a Hamada? I mean, what kind of creature he is?
Kostadis Roussos: He's a fiendish-born fire giant.
Dimos: Feed what?
Kostadis Roussos: A fiend born… he's a fiend… he's the one… sorry, let me see if I can explain this.
Kostadis Roussos: What's happened is Grast, the Demon Lord.
Dimos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Very powerful creature.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, great. Ruler of one of the abyssal plains.
Dimos: Great.
Kostadis Roussos: Has infused several… has infused fire giants with…
Dimos: Demonic blood, let's say.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, so… and so he's the big… he's their leader. So Hamad is their… Sorry, not Hamad, I keep saying the wrong name.
Kostadis Roussos: Helday, sorry, Helday Hellspawn is the leader… is the leader of the Fire Giant and Demonic Forces.
Dimos: Okay.
Dimos: So, if we kill him… By chance, start… Doing the chaotic things.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, that's what they do.
Dimos: I think.
Kostadis Roussos: Does that make sense?
Dimos: Yes, but how that's gonna distract grust?
Kostadis Roussos: Well…
Kostadis Roussos: So just as a side note, the only person… the only people who know that grass is going to show up are you guys. Nobody else knows that… nobody else knows about the other part of the plan.
Dimos: K…
Dimos: So… He just doesn't know that we're gonna sue up.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, Grass doesn't know that you're… that you know about him. More importantly, nobody else in that room knows about the fact but what Alder told you.
Dimos: Should we tell them?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, the problem with telling them is that, you know, all of a sudden you've turned it fighting a fire giant to fighting a demon lord.
Dimos: Yes, but we kinda have to plan for fighting in Demon Lord.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, nobody…
Dimos: Because we're gonna fight a demon lord.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, but that's a you problem, not on everybody else's problem.
Nicholas Roussos: That's not an entire…
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Does that make sense?
Dimos: Yes, but we can make it their problem, too.
Kostadis Roussos: You mean, oh, you make…
Dimos: So you're telling me double E doesn't know that grass is gonna show up?
Dimos: in…
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Nobody knows that. You guys, Alder is desperate, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: What do you mean? Come on.
Dimos: Okay, soap.
Dimos: If you say they don't know, they don't know.
Kostadis Roussos: they don't know, right? I mean…
Kostadis Roussos: And they don't know for… they don't know for a variety of reasons. Some would never think to ask.
Kostadis Roussos: So, the First Lord of Hillsfar wouldn't even think to ask. He doesn't think in terms of demonic possessions, alright?
Kostadis Roussos: He sees fire giants. Fire giants are something that you kill, and you defeat.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? The only person who might have an intuition is Solomon, and he's not talking.
Dimos: Because she wants chaos to unfold, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Because he wants… he… he… because he's a wizard, and you never know what the wizards want.
Kostadis Roussos: Rylia… Rylera is a drow… is a drow, and, you know, she… she doesn't think about these things, right?
Kostadis Roussos: And if she ever does. Quilbrin is a drow fighter, he doesn't think about these things, right? Give me a… give me a pointy thing… give me a thing at the end that I can kill at the end of a pointy arrow or stick, and I will… and that's how he thinks, right?
Dimos: Okay.
Dimos: The never answers…
Kostadis Roussos: The InverAnswers leader and their sub-leader have disappeared.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, Elasta was disintegrated, and Velasta has…
Dimos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So whoever's now in charge, who knows, is, like, the number 3 in charge.
Kostadis Roussos: And what you know about evil cults is the number 1 has all the information, the number 2 has whatever information she was able to glean from the number 1, and the number 3 has no idea what the hell is going on.
Dimos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So, so your assumption, like, I mean, so she's kind of.
Dimos: that lives with double E, the mind flare, and the…
Dimos: I don't remember what curriculum is that.
Kostadis Roussos: Which one?
Dimos: Next to Solomon, the big master.
Kostadis Roussos: The big mushroom.
Dimos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Now, the big mushroom knows a lot about what's going inside of Spore Dome, but pays zero attention to what's going outside of Spore Dome.
Dimos: Okay, the monster?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, you could always talk to the Mind Flayer.
Dimos: So the mind of their knows.
Kostadis Roussos: No, I said you could always talk to the Mind Flayer.
Dimos: He's a mindset, he can… he can read our thoughts.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, yes, but you could prevent him from reading your thoughts, right?
Kostadis Roussos: So, yes, I mean, when he reads… so, yes, I'm just saying that that's… the Mind Flayer…
Kostadis Roussos: Is, is another player in all of this.
Dimos: Okay, so we're probably gonna need to talk to the mine fair.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, but I just want to be clear, like, every… nobody at this point in time, other… nobody… you… for a fact, the fact that Grask may show up is not… if I said it, was misspoken. Nobody… everybody believes that all they have to do is go to Miramidra and defeat
Kostadis Roussos: Helder Hillsborough.
Kostadis Roussos: The fire giants, and all is safe.
Dimos: Yeah, sure, sure, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? I mean, so your choice is to tell them all what's really going on, or to keep silent.
Dimos: I mean, we can say to specific people, like, not…
Dimos: The… the leaders of the creatures that we want to go to do the first attack.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so the one… so the people you know are in charge, in their own little way, is Elisil.
Kostadis Roussos: Palasso is the overall leader, right?
Dimos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Solomon is… the drow are all looking at Solomon, who's kind of proven his power and lethality.
Dimos: But we don't… Solomon doesn't care about them, and so…
Kostadis Roussos: He's got his own agendas.
Kostadis Roussos: He's a… he's a…
Kostadis Roussos: And what you do know from the… when you went into Meramedra before is that Solomon tried to make a deal with the fire giants.
Kostadis Roussos: Remember you went through his laboratory?
Dimos: Yes, correct.
Kostadis Roussos: So, Solomon… what game Solomon's playing, you have no idea.
Dimos: Okay, so what I'm hearing is probably it could be good to talk to Double E and the manager.
Kostadis Roussos: Those were… yes, I mean… and, like, first… the first lord, Voom might suddenly decide that, you know, fighting Demon Lords, fighting fire giants.
Dimos: something.
Kostadis Roussos: Fighting demon lords.
Dimos: He's above his pay grade, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, that's what heroes are for, and you know, quite frankly, he's not about to, like…
Dimos: in the game.
Kostadis Roussos: So, so that's your, that's your, situation.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, let me just do one more thing. I need to create another handout.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so,
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so this did not copy, this is… these are the, the objectives you have. All right. So you approach, a la… so you approach Elisil Elendil. All right. She looks at you and says.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, I have a thousand things to prepare. What do you need?
Dimos: Nothing important, just wanted you to be informed about a small… Possibility that we're gonna have
Dimos: at some point in the midst of battle, like, like, you know, just grasp, there's a possibility he will show up, but that's it. Continue with your preparations.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, so you're trying to throw out a hint.
Dimos: Yes, I mean, I told here, but…
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, roll the descec… roll… I don't know, like, what should we roll?
Dimos: Why do I roll?
Kostadis Roussos: Are you trying to fish from her? Is that what I'm hearing?
Dimos: I mean, no, I just want you to know that… oh.
Dimos: We have this information, you should probably know and Help us deal with it.
Kostadis Roussos: She looks at… okay, roll… okay, let me see, what does she do? Does she… what does she…
Dimos: You know, stunt. What?
Dimos: I'm guessing she didn't understand?
Kostadis Roussos: No. Now roll your insight to see if you notice that.
Dimos: Inside, Brahm Grimm has… inside,
Dimos: Is 13 good enough, or does he get help?
Kostadis Roussos: 13's good enough. Bromgrim, notices that Alasso kind of, like, has no, like, is just going, great, you know, people who don't know Benny better are saying things they don't know anything about.
Dimos: Okay, so it ignores it by choice.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, like, she doesn't… she doesn't draw the connection.
Dimos: Okay, so Diane's.
Kostadis Roussos: So, turns, so…
Dimos: More straightforward to have.
Kostadis Roussos: Sorry, let me put it this way. Adventurer shows up and says, oh, Demonic Lord may show up.
Dimos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Like, Alasso Elendil has heard that about a billion times in her life, right?
Kostadis Roussos: It's kind of like when you're the leader of an organization, everybody's coming to you and telling you the disaster that might hit.
Dimos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So, she's kind of like…
Kostadis Roussos: So she's… you're just one more person telling her about one more thing that might go wrong.
Dimos: with a greater possibility than Synosh.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, so do you want to go talk, tell her, be more blunt with her?
Dimos: What, sorry?
Kostadis Roussos: Are you gonna be more direct with her?
Dimos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: She stops and looks at you and goes, what do you know?
Dimos: that… That is the plan for him to escape, so he will probably go to… Mermaida.
Kostadis Roussos: She goes, escaped from what?
Kostadis Roussos: Do you want to tell her the whole plan, or do you want to tell her some of the plan?
Dimos: Some of the plan.
Kostadis Roussos: She looks at you and says, Where did you learn this?
Dimos: Does it matter?
Kostadis Roussos: She looks at you and says, if you want me to change anything, it absolutely matters.
Dimos: So, you're telling me that you don't trust…
Kostadis Roussos: No, I'm telling you I have an army to lead to war, and you're telling me a few minutes before I'm about to lead them to war that I have to change my plans about some hypothetical outcome that may occur based on information I have no possibility of verifying.
Dimos: Okay, where did I know from?
Kostadis Roussos: So you tell her about Alder, right?
Dimos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: She looks at you and laughs.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. Fortunately, Brom Grimm has the signature.
Dimos: Thank God.
Kostadis Roussos: Fortunately, Rob Grimm has the signature. Alessio goes, Alder? You spoke to Alder?
Dimos: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: She goes… She looks at the signature.
Kostadis Roussos: And so, this is all part of that Harper's bas… that bastard Harper's plans. She's sending us to get killed because to clean up the mess that she and her gang created?
Dimos: Look, I'm not telling you that you have to get killed, I'm just saying that I need some help to prepare for if that happens, that it's possible to 100%.
Kostadis Roussos: Alasso looks at it and says, nothing changes. We still… without… if the fire giants… you won't be able to… she pauses and thinks. If Grass is planning to show up here to escape, we still have to defeat the fire giants.
Dimos: Yes, but… The question is, if we have the fried gents being chaotic.
Dimos: I don't know if it will help us to… Good.
Kostadis Roussos: She goes, well, you'll never be able to get… if you… the only… our only hope, and she looks at you and says, oh god, I'm really gonna say this. Our only hope is if the four of you manage… five of you manage to make it to Grast. The only way you're going to make it to Grast is if we make it into Mare Midra and defeat the fire giants.
Dimos: Okay, great. So we agree.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, so the plan has not changed.
Nicholas Roussos: Yep, basically.
Dimos: Well, you're not gonna have the full help from us, because we have to be prepared for grass.
Kostadis Roussos: If we don't succeed at getting into Merr Midra, you won't get to Grast.
Dimos: Yes, we're gonna get you to Invermedra, but from there on, you're alone.
Kostadis Roussos: She looks at you, you look at her…
Kostadis Roussos: She pauses and said, weren't we always alone?
Dimos: No?
Kostadis Roussos: She's not very happy with what you just said, but realizes she has nothing else. She turns to you and says, I have nothing more to discuss.
Kostadis Roussos: I have a war to… I have a war to win, and you have assignments to make.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: So, she's not very happy, role in insight?
Dimos: Is 12 enough, or does she get help?
Kostadis Roussos: No, that's not nowhere anywhere near enough.
Kostadis Roussos: You rolled a 2?
Dimos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, roll again.
Dimos: So, he gets help, and probably Bartic inspiration.
Dimos: 15, so I guess that doesn't… that's not enough. Roll your butt.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, fuck.
Dimos: plus 520.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so that's enough. Alright.
Dimos: Great.
Kostadis Roussos: Elasso Elendil is not very happy that you guys are gonna hold back, but she's still expecting you to… to do everything you can to get into Mary Midra.
Dimos: is.
Kostadis Roussos: And…
Dimos: Probably gonna go kill the… guy that controls the fire science.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: But that after that, your objectives and her objectives are different.
Dimos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: So she gets that.
Dimos: Great.
Kostadis Roussos: Does Felcourt, at this point in time, mention the other objective he has, which is to raid the… the tower?
Nicholas Roussos: Yeah, no, so the reason I don't mention it, because the plan is to get in the tower.
Nicholas Roussos: Get drunk.
Nicholas Roussos: black out drunk, and appear outside of the book, so that if scryed, they don't know who stole it.
Nicholas Roussos: Because I won't know that I stole it. I'll just know that I have it.
Kostadis Roussos: Fair enough.
Nicholas Roussos: That's the plan! And so we're not telling nobody.
Kostadis Roussos: Nobody's knowing about the plan?
Kostadis Roussos: All right? Okay. The other person you need to go… the other person… so that's what you learn from a lasso. The other… the other person you could go talk to is whom?
Dimos: the bind flare?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Dimos: Yes, I think I would like to talk to the mindflare.
Kostadis Roussos: The mind flayer looks at you and says.
Kostadis Roussos: You are the one… you are the ones that helped us with the rogue thought.
Dimos: Yes?
Kostadis Roussos: You have helped my colony.
Dimos: Great.
Kostadis Roussos: You could help further.
Dimos: Well, you know, in my.
Kostadis Roussos: In my village.
Dimos: You help me, I help you. Well, I help you, so you have to help me.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, roll your persuasion.
Dimos: Can Bramgraim do it?
Kostadis Roussos: Anybody could do it.
Dimos: Okay, great, because Bramg has the best one.
Kostadis Roussos: You know you're a… you know you're a bard, right?
Dimos: 17?
Dimos: Is that enough, or does he need the birding inspiration?
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Kostadis Roussos: What is it?
Kostadis Roussos: Is that enough?
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so what did you roll?
Dimos: 17.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Whom's… Whom turns to you and says, Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: What were you trying to convince them? Sorry, I was trying to dig up some notes.
Dimos: We help him, it's time for him to help us.
Kostadis Roussos: He pauses. It is my understanding from… and he mentions the guy, the Mind Flayer, that we already gave you two magical items of significant power and wealth.
Dimos: Yes… Did they?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, they did.
Kostadis Roussos: And so, as I see it, the ledger is clean.
Kostadis Roussos: He pauses and says, What is it that you wish?
Dimos: Okay, we need help with class, so what do you want for us to do for you?
Kostadis Roussos: You wish help from foregrast?
Dimos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: What is it that the prince of… the prince grasped is coming?
Dimos: Most likely, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: This forces us to reconsider our involvement in this war.
Dimos: Oh no, you don't have to, you don't have to.
Kostadis Roussos: Why?
Dimos: Just have to say ET.
Dimos: Because we got him.
Kostadis Roussos: bosses. Well, then if you got him, then you need nothing from us.
Dimos: We got some with the help of you.
Kostadis Roussos: Why would we risk ourselves? The Mind Flayers have survived demonic incursions. Pauses. Probably engineered a few.
Kostadis Roussos: What I have learned, and what my colony has learned, is that the best solution to a demonic incursion is to be anywhere but near the demonic incursion.
Nicholas Roussos: Oh, come on, when's the last time you got to fight… to fight a demonic incursion?
Kostadis Roussos: We've been fighting one for the past 6 months, to a year, to 2 years, ever since the blink happened.
Nicholas Roussos: Yeah, Steve, don't you want to finish it up?
Dimos: I like how Felcor plays with his ego.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, roll, roll, roll your persuasion.
Nicholas Roussos: Yeah, I don't have a good persuasion, dude.
Dimos: Yeah, Brian would…
Nicholas Roussos: I actually have a plus 5.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, like you're doing…
Dimos: Okay, yeah, you do it then, yeah.
Nicholas Roussos: I'll do it, I'll do it.
Dimos: Yeah, you do it.
Nicholas Roussos: with some help.
Dimos: Of course.
Nicholas Roussos: 17.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, Turns to you.
Kostadis Roussos: Looks at you and goes, what a tasty brain.
Kostadis Roussos: And then…
Dimos: So you have to sing him when he's drunk.
Kostadis Roussos: It goes… Yes, yes, I must see him when he's drunk.
Nicholas Roussos: Oh, you will.
Kostadis Roussos: Akritas carefully prepares her bow, just in case the Mind Flayer gets any tasty ideas.
Kostadis Roussos: The mind player says, what help do you need?
Dimos: I don't know how you can help us, actually, what you can provide.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so what he will do is he will provide you with a list of Grasts' abilities.
Dimos: That's… a good start? Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: And he says, But anything else will be… we'll have to reevaluate as the situation unfolds.
Dimos: Okay…
Kostadis Roussos: So you're not gonna go fight blind, in terms of fighting crust.
Dimos: Okay, that's… that's… that's something.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: So, you step… you… so you're… the… the Vine Flayer walks away, and,
Kostadis Roussos: Who but a short halfling who looks like a middle-aged.
Kostadis Roussos: Rogue shows up and pulls Bromgum to the side. Do you guys follow him or not?
Dimos: we trust Bram Grimm.
Kostadis Roussos: Bromgrim speaks to her, comes back. I have bad news.
Dimos: Be careful what to say.
Dimos: What? Be careful about what you're gonna say.
Kostadis Roussos: Solomon Nedrazak, the archmage of Sithmor Kane, is the key to keeping our alliance together with his fellow drow.
Dimos: gang?
Kostadis Roussos: He explains… Alder explains that… Alder explained to me that the only reason why they haven't been fighting each other is because they're all terrified of what Solomon will do to each one… to the one faction that tries to kill him and fails.
Kostadis Roussos: She also pauses, and he also pauses and says, apparently the drow have this thing where if you try to kill one of their… try to kill a faction and fail to kill every single last member of the faction, the other factions are honor-bound to exterminate you.
Dimos: I don't see the problem.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, so if somebody fails to kill Solomon Nedrazak, then the other factions will destroy that faction.
Dimos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So, they're all honor-bound to, apparently, this is how drows society avoids descending into permanent civil war.
Dimos: Okay…
Kostadis Roussos: I asked the same question you're asking, Diane. There's a story, I don't know how true it is, but in Menzobaranzen, there was a house that tried to… a noble house, that tried to kill a noble… another noble house, and they killed everyone except for one child.
Dimos: Please don't tell me that one side was solem on Nedrazak.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no, it wasn't Solomon, necessarily, completely unrelated.
Kostadis Roussos: And so, the remaining noble houses of Menzo Boranzen came and exterminated the attack, the house that failed to kill that one child.
Dimos: Okay, I don't understand how is that our problem.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, well, that's… I'm just trying to explain to you the situation.
Kostadis Roussos: The drow…
Kostadis Roussos: We must protect them at all costs, so we can keep the drow in the Alliance, and keep them from potentially killing each other or being another foe.
Kostadis Roussos: pauses. Unfortunately, we have heard that Dorina Taran, the former ruler of Sithmor Kane, and a vampire drow cleric of Kiran Saleh, has been seen in the area, and vowed revenge upon Solomon. We cannot afford her meddling.
Dimos: Okay, so we have to protect Solomon.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, you also realize that, so, make an history check.
Dimos: History tech.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Dimos: Okay, 20, not natural.
Kostadis Roussos: That's fine. You recognize the name Durina Tsaran as being the same name, having the same last name as Velostad Tsaran, and they were both clerics of Kiransule.
Dimos: So we have to, to protect Solomon from, bloodthirsty… Pretty true.
Kostadis Roussos: Right. No, so you've got a vampire, and so what… Bob Romgraham looks at you and goes, yes, Diane, you correctly figured it out.
Kostadis Roussos: Dorina is… Velosta's aunt.
Dimos: It could be from the other part of the family.
Kostadis Roussos: Peace.
Dimos: Good and happy.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no.
Dimos: That's the problem.
Kostadis Roussos: them, they are good and happy. Velosta's pursuit of vengeance hinged on Dorina losing power.
Kostadis Roussos: If Dorino.
Dimos: if they're…
Kostadis Roussos: If they find… if Dorina's… if Dorina finds out Solomon's alive…
Dimos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: She'll want to kill him, and she'll tell Velosta, which will cause Velosta to change her orientation.
Dimos: I think Velasa knows that Nedrazak is alive, no?
Kostadis Roussos: No, she doesn't.
Dimos: Tulture.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, you didn't… no, you did not. She did not know… she did not… you told her that the fire giants killed her.
Dimos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So you… now you're, like, at this point in time, you can't even keep track of all of the lies you've told everybody.
Dimos: So, what I understand is that.
Nicholas Roussos: Let's just go to war already.
Dimos: Yes, the ant doesn't have to come near here, let's start the war, let's…
Dimos: Let's say, Roman, go back to your…
Dimos: I mean, how they don't know that Solomon is alive? I mean…
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, because…
Dimos: Because we were talking to all of them, And Solomon appeared.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, yes. Velasta doesn't know, because she already left for Never… she already left for Miramidra on her own.
Dimos: Okay, so… The other creatures from her faction wouldn't tell her?
Kostadis Roussos: They haven't spoken to her yet.
Dimos: K… So even if her aunt sees him now, We have time.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I'm just telling you what that… yes, but… yes, I'm just saying, but she… she… I just want… I just want you to be aware that, like, that is a… that is another time bomb landing on your… on your, on your plate.
Dimos: Okay.
Dimos: I know exactly what will happen in Miramidra, but it's fine.
Dimos: I know exactly what you're gonna pull out.
Dimos: at exactly which moments you're gonna do it. So, it's fine.
Kostadis Roussos: What? I have no idea what you're talking about, man.
Dimos: Of course not, of course not, nothing. Everything will go as planned, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: And, and, just so you know, the, the… what's his name?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so I'm just gonna put this, all players… Save changes, alright.
Kostadis Roussos: So, this is, that mission.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. So, so let's go to… let's go… so while this is going on…
Kostadis Roussos: You now have to… if you go to the, I think, what to do, you see that thing that says what to do?
Dimos: The what to do, what to do.
Dimos: Yes. Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so these are… so… Dude…
Kostadis Roussos: Let me just tell you what you need to do.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so it should be a little bit more legible now.
Dimos: I will go to the bathroom for one minute, and I'll stop.
Kostadis Roussos: So these, these are, these are the… so the, the, what you need to do here…
Dimos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: is…
Kostadis Roussos: Took me, like, just let me just tell you that trying to figure out how to read this module took me, like, 6 weeks.
Dimos: Until you find the worlds, I'm going to go to the bottom.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, go to the bathroom, go to the bathroom.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so what you need to do…
Kostadis Roussos: Is decide who you're gonna send to each one of these fact… to each one of these locations.
Kostadis Roussos: So there's 1, 2, 3, 4, 5…
Kostadis Roussos: There should be 6 listed. You got… do you see 6 on the… the… the… the…
Kostadis Roussos: It's been true about this.
Kostadis Roussos: Someone was missing.
Kostadis Roussos: So you get to send one of the allies you've accumulated to one of these factions. I forgot to add the stone giants as well.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so, if you look at what to do, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Alara is basically… EE is asking you to assign… to pick two of these ba… two of these options to go attack.
Kostadis Roussos: Yourselves, and then assign your factions to the other ones.
Dimos: Okay, so we have 4 functions, and we need to get rid of two, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, you've got… you take two, and then the other four… Right, so you have…
Kostadis Roussos: You have the never-answers, who are currently leaderless.
Kostadis Roussos: You have Quilbrin, Right?
Kostadis Roussos: You have Verun, you have Raylu, Alara, and you have the Stone Giants. Those are the factions you can go help… who can go help each one of these, things, and then you have to pick two that the party's gonna do.
Dimos: cake…
Kostadis Roussos: Next week.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Dimos: Okay, so I'm guessing, do we know…
Dimos: So I'm guessing that in neither of all of them.
Dimos: He's the guy that we need to kill, right?
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, this is just to get in… this is the first phase of the battle.
Kostadis Roussos: So this is the part.
Dimos: Does it matter where we're going?
Kostadis Roussos: Does it matter where you go? No, what matters is that you're successful.
Dimos: And it doesn't matter where… what assignment we put to each of the bases, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Let me just check that.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, no, it does matter. If you send somebody against something that they're well-matched, they're more likely to be successful.
Dimos: Okay, so I'm seeing here, like, we have the friendly dead, so… they're… Probably we want to…
Dimos: Arvas…
Kostadis Roussos: That never answers.
Dimos: I remember the name.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, that never answers.
Dimos: But never answers, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so you want to send them there? Alright.
Dimos: I'm trying to understand how we should figure out which
Dimos: function goes better, I guess, the pace, but…
Kostadis Roussos: So stone… just to… so just to, you know, stone giants, you know, fight well against fire giants, so anything that involves fighting fire giants, probably sending stone giants against is a good idea.
Dimos: Okay,
Dimos: If I read correctly, the only place that has giants, probably has giants, is the northern forward.
Kostadis Roussos: The northern, the northern forward or eastern base.
Dimos: Oh, in the Eastern, I didn't see…
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, so then the northern…
Dimos: advanced.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, then the northern and the western.
Kostadis Roussos: Just pick one.
Dimos: Are you sure, because I… okay, so the Northern, let's say northern.
Kostadis Roussos: But… Oh, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So, in preparation for the attack on the Northern Gate, a group will approach the Nurbar Cave and eliminate any giants, so that's…
Kostadis Roussos: the Northern Gate. In preparation for the attack on, a group will approach a nearby cave to set up this approach's poorly trained
Kostadis Roussos: This one, the eastern-based apparently doesn't have any giants mentioned, right?
Dimos: neither the Western one.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, yes, but you're getting towards the gate of the city, so that's why you might… you're more likely to see a… to see fire giants. Does that make sense?
Dimos: Okay, yeah. So, in another forward base, we extend the Giants.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so you send the giants to the forward base. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: The giants go, huzzah!
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, where do you send, who else do you send?
Dimos: So we have the… so which are the other functions that we have?
Kostadis Roussos: The hidden.
Dimos: And what are they good for?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, the audition with them was to sneak around and steal something.
Kostadis Roussos: Right. The hidden are the guys who practice secret sneaking around, so they might be a good target for this.
Dimos: Okay, I'm trying to see if there's any of those that we need to steal something, but…
Dimos: Or be sneaky.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, yeah, these accepting to take advantage of this newly and scout its length to determine if it is indeed one of those that feeds the lake of blood.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, so this is a scouting mission.
Dimos: the underdoor.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Dimos: Yes, but as I read, they understand that we have to be inside the city to go to the anteur.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me just make sure…
Dimos: If the party chooses this objective, it must be the second encounter, since you will be inside the city if you succeed.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, yeah, it's just that if you take… if you want to take it, you just need to pick something else first, that's all it's saying.
Dimos: Okay, so we are gonna do the thieves to the underdoor.
Kostadis Roussos: You're gonna send the thieves to the underdoor, okay? It's about you, not about, like…
Kostadis Roussos: If you… if the party chooses it, it's their second mission. Otherwise, you can… it's just assigned to somebody.
Dimos: Yeah, okay.
Dimos: Okay, and probably the friendly dev should go to the…
Kostadis Roussos: The never answers.
Dimos: They're never… yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Dimos: Seems like a good fit.
Dimos: Right?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes?
Dimos: Okay, and what's the last function?
Kostadis Roussos: So the next one is,
Kostadis Roussos: Relera's slaves, and Grundar's Duergar.
Kostadis Roussos: They're, you know, send them to one of the bases to go help there.
Dimos: So, those doesn't matter if they're going to the eastern or the western one.
Kostadis Roussos: No, it doesn't.
Dimos: Okay, so we're gonna send them to, let's say, Eastern one, and we're gonna get the Western and the Fortify Gains.
Kostadis Roussos: You're gonna take the Western?
Dimos: Yes?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright? That leaves Quilbrin's Drow to take on the northern base.
Dimos: No, in the northern forward base goes the fires… the stones ends.
Kostadis Roussos: So where do you want to send? Quilbrin's drow looks at you and says, let us not forget our arrangement.
Dimos: Arrangement, arrangement…
Kostadis Roussos: Everybody else goes in first, and then they go in, so soften the targets up.
Kostadis Roussos: They're gonna be kept in reserve.
Dimos: I mean, they can go to the 45 Games after the Stone Giants have…
Dimos: Capture one of the forward-based positions.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so you're gonna tell them to back that up, is that what I'm hearing?
Dimos: Yes.
Dimos: Because then… because if I understand correctly, when one of the forward-based positions is captured, they will forfeit the 45 gains, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Dimos: Okay, so yeah, we're gonna send them there, and we're going to the western forward, basically.
Kostadis Roussos: So, oh, so you're not going to keep any faction in reserve, is that what I'm hearing?
Dimos: Do we need to?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, I mean…
Kostadis Roussos: If you keep a faction in reserve, when… if Grass shows up, you might have somebody who can help you.
Dimos: Okay, we're gonna…
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, look, but before you do that, you know that if you keep any faction in reserve, all the other factions know that you just did that.
Dimos: So, if we keep in…
Dimos: I think we're…
Dimos: I mean, can't we say to the other functions that it's part of the plan to stay back?
Kostadis Roussos: You can try, yes.
Dimos: I guess we're trying.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so, Relera, of course, objects. She's like…
Kostadis Roussos: you know, she's like, what is this? The drow knights should be defending whatever. So she's like, she's vociferously objecting.
Dimos: No, no, no, you have to think about it, like, if we need an extra help to one of the posts, we can send that army to help, so having a backup to, as a joke, go anywhere is a pretty good plan.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, roll, roll a persuasion.
Dimos: Frustration… 25.
Kostadis Roussos: She is convinced. You notice that Solomon Nedrazak smiles.
Dimos: Can I hit him?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh yeah, you can totally hit him.
Kostadis Roussos: I mean, you can totally try to hit him.
Kostadis Roussos: He smiles.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so we've set up the situation for next week. Hold on, but there's one more detail. Since you said you wanted to be a member of the Lord's Alliance…
Dimos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Dimos: We can do it after the war.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, they have a mission for you.
Dimos: That's why I said after the war.
Nicholas Roussos: Ledger and get out. I don't care.
Dimos: Indeed.
Nicholas Roussos: Underworld battle or whatever.
Kostadis Roussos: I was like, I hate that.
Nicholas Roussos: They got it figured out. I'm trying to get my ledger, I'm trying to get outta here.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: So, one of… a member of the Order of the Gauntlet approaches you, and Hans says.
Kostadis Roussos: We've seen you, we've seen how, Dad, we've seen how you've been focused for good.
Kostadis Roussos: And we know that you are not a member of the Order of the Gauntlet, and we know that you do not…
Kostadis Roussos: Yet swear fealty to our cause, but we thought we should tell you of a mission that we have.
Kostadis Roussos: And it's got all the stench of the kind of mission that the Order of the Gauntlet has. In the middle of the war.
Kostadis Roussos: What are they interested in?
Dimos: Save people?
Kostadis Roussos: Order of the Gauntlet.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, exactly. Nearby is a cavern… here, you should see it. Nearby is a cavern known as the Cave of Black Whisterers, where a large group of dwarves were once surprised, then slaughtered by the drow of Sith Morkane. The cavern has since been haunted by their death.
Kostadis Roussos: What the others do not know is that the leaders of the dwarves has risen as a mummy of some power, and it is evil forces that… the dwarves to languish in undeath. A relative, Glenna Moonsmith, the owner of the pudding Plow and the stop, whom you know very well.
Kostadis Roussos: Has approached us and begged us to lay her ancestor to rest permanently.
Dimos: Okay, so we have to go fight a mummy.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, I mean, just… you do recall that this is, in fact, Charles' girlfriend.
Dimos: Yeah, yeah, I know who Lemon Smith is.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: You can choose to not do it, but…
Kostadis Roussos: And, and, and, and… but you, you, you notice the disappro… you've noticed that the guy would be very… the very big disapproval.
Dimos: And we'll go first there, and then to the western… western base?
Kostadis Roussos: We can… we can definitely see what happens.
Dimos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Felcor.
Kostadis Roussos: A member of the Zentarim.
Nicholas Roussos: Who are they again?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, you know who the Zendarim are. You're in character… actually, in character, you also don't know who the Zendarim are.
Nicholas Roussos: Yeah, I forget who they are.
Kostadis Roussos: So, remember, in the north, there are five factions, and one of them, the Zentaren, are basically the guys who want to rule… who engage in… who want to engage in trade, where they collect all… where they collect all the money.
Nicholas Roussos: Huh.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? And they're engaged in all kind of… all kinds of trade.
Kostadis Roussos: And they've heard that… Yeah, I'm about to explain to you what I mean by trade.
Nicholas Roussos: We take stuff…
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no, no, they trade in stuff.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Nicholas Roussos: I get it, I get it.
Kostadis Roussos: the Centaura, and so they go.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes… one of them goes, we have some of the best operatives, but without good stock, nothing works. Word is that many of Grast's children are in the city. The older ones… well, actually, they start off by this way. Mr. Felcor.
Nicholas Roussos: Olden Wood. Olden… Olden, sec, sorry.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold up.
Nicholas Roussos: Old and done, sorry, old and done. Old and done.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, that… oh, you're giving your real name out, not your fake name.
Nicholas Roussos: Yeah. Mr. Owen died, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, yes, he goes…
Nicholas Roussos: What was the misspelling again?
Kostadis Roussos: I'll have to look it up, I'll have to… let me just.
Dimos: Oh, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: It's just hysterical! So…
Nicholas Roussos: Cool and Don.
Kostadis Roussos: I finally figured it out, because I added a check in the tools to, like, check the name of the campaign.
Kostadis Roussos: And, like, it's like, I can't convert this file. I go, why can't you convert this file? Because that's the name of the party.
Kostadis Roussos: All… all when… yeah,
Nicholas Roussos: Just send it in the chat.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, I'll send it to you. Olden Wood. That's the, he's known as Olden Wood.
Nicholas Roussos: Yeah, almost unlimited, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Who goes?
Kostadis Roussos: We, we've, heard… we've been very impressed with your work.
Nicholas Roussos: Which works?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, I mean, your ability to… your masterful team's ability to move goods from one location to another.
Nicholas Roussos: Yes, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: And, there, there have been… and, and it, there was a rumor
Kostadis Roussos: that after you left the city of Merh Midra, an arcanealoth tower was breached.
Dimos: It is deep.
Nicholas Roussos: Perhaps.
Kostadis Roussos: And there was also a rumor that the Cambians of Mayor Midra have decided they're no longer supporting the fire giants.
Kostadis Roussos: And we believe that that shows great promise. Great, great promise.
Nicholas Roussos: Okay…
Kostadis Roussos: And we would be more than happy to help in the movement of any goods out of the Underdark to an appropriate buyer for a small, shipping fee.
Nicholas Roussos: Oh, I don't sell the stuff that I get.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, if you were to find anything that was, how shall we say, needed to be moved…
Nicholas Roussos: There might be a few items that might be needed.
Kostadis Roussos: That needed to be moved in a discrete way, where the provenance and the buyer…
Nicholas Roussos: I whisper to die in a…
Nicholas Roussos: I'm gonna give them something so that if people try and hunt me down for the ledger, they think these guys have it.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, he goes, but… but one thing we would, as a good token of good faith, and perhaps is to cement our working relationship.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah. They're apparently Grast has children in the city.
Nicholas Roussos: You want me to get him, don't you?
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no, no, we don't want the older ones, but a few of the newborns, we could raise them right.
Kostadis Roussos: As true members of the back.
Kostadis Roussos: black network, with all the powers of a demon lord. That would be a powerful operative…
Kostadis Roussos: That would be a powerful operative indeed. He pauses. There are rumors that these children might be found somewhere in or near Castle Merbidrav.
Kostadis Roussos: And pauses. The Black Network would be forever indebted to you for…
Nicholas Roussos: Oh, yeah, absolutely, I'd love to, I'd love to,
Dimos: Hmm.
Nicholas Roussos: I'm assuming…
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Nicholas Roussos: Diane, do you have something to say?
Dimos: it's… your problem…
Nicholas Roussos: What problem? There's no problem right here.
Kostadis Roussos: By the way, I'm assuming that, Emerald Enclave babe, Harper dude who hate the Xantarum do not know about this potential side quest.
Dimos: They don't know about any side quests. They think that we're going to work.
Kostadis Roussos: And nor does Order of the Gauntlet dude, who's, like, you know, all about the good, right? So this is a Felcourt…
Kostadis Roussos: They're trying to have this discreetly away from everybody else, Felcor.
Kostadis Roussos: In fact, what they do is they sit down while you were… while you're sitting there, they offered you a very expensive and very rare bottle of wine.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, they're trying to wine and dine you, man.
Nicholas Roussos: No, I understand.
Nicholas Roussos: I've told him this, but my plan is, you know.
Nicholas Roussos: I'll give them something to sneak out, and then I'll pocket the ledger, so that if somebody… or, like, I'll give them a few things, so if somebody tries to find the ledger, they'll go after the Ventarum, not me.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh.
Dimos: Found out.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Nicholas Roussos: If they find out, they'll go after the Dentarum.
Kostadis Roussos: So, just as a… what you do realize is one thing you could do is you could give them something from the, the…
Nicholas Roussos: That's what I'm gonna do.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, you're gonna give them something?
Nicholas Roussos: I'm gonna get not just the ledger, but I'm gonna keep the ledger, but I'll give them other stuff from there.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, got it, got it. You'll give them other things from, from the, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, okay, so I think we've got the battle scene set up for next week.
Nicholas Roussos: Great.
Kostadis Roussos: All these soldiers march out, there's lots of cheering, huzzah, huzzah, huzzah.
Kostadis Roussos: Solomon Nedrazak is, of course, smiling, his curious and cryptic smile, and Double E says, we're not… looks at you and says, if grass shows up, not all of these people are dead. I hope you have a plan.
Dimos: Don't want to worry about it.
Dimos: Everything is under control.
Kostadis Roussos: She goes, we have no choice but to do this.
Kostadis Roussos: She pauses and says, alright.
Kostadis Roussos: She looks at you and does that heroic thing. Diane, I remember when we first met.
Dimos: A.
Kostadis Roussos: I didn't think we would be here, rushing into death or to glory.
Dimos: We're not gonna die.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, if the Demon Lord captures us, I really do hope we die.
Dimos: I mean, yeah, but if we go to the mentality that we're gonna die and lose, then we shouldn't go.
Nicholas Roussos: Hey, don't worry, I've been making this really strong alcohol, it'll knock you out if you get captured.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, with that heroic… Double E looks at you, smiles, and is obviously encouraged, and puts on her… puts on her helmet and heads off.
Kostadis Roussos: to her… to man her position. And with that, we end… we end the battle preparations.
Nicholas Roussos: Great.
Dimos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: I hope you guys had fun. I definitely enjoyed the squirming, watching, members of the… newly-minted members of the Order of the Gauntlet, the Zhintaran…
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Take care, guys.
Nicholas Roussos: We can't…
Dimos: Bye.